kenyalaw.org 2016-11-25

# Kenya Law: Privacy Policy and Disclaimer

1.  **Our Commitment to Privacy**  
The National Council for Law Reporting values your privacy. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home page and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.  
   
2. **  Acceptance Privacy Policy Terms**  
Please note that our Privacy Policy applies to the “ www.kenyalaw.org ” Web Site only. Your usage of this Web Site constitutes acceptance of this privacy policy and any modifications made to it.  
   
3. **  Application of Privacy Policy**  
This Policy applies only to the information collected by the National Council for Law Reporting from the users of our Web Site (www.kenyalaw.org ). It does not apply to information collected by us in any other way, including offline.  
   
4.  **Links**  
Our Web Site contains links to other web sites operated by third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of such third party web sites and this Policy does not apply to those web sites.  
   
5. **  The Information We Collect**  
a) Non-Personal Information Collected and How it is Used   
Our Web Site is not set up to automatically collect personally identifiable information from each visitor to our Web Site. It does recognize the home server of visitors,but not e-mail addresses. For example,we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use,but not the names,addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our Web Site. The technical information we do collect is used only for internal purposes by our technical support staff.  
   
Our Web Site does track certain information about the visits to our Web Site. For example,we compile statistics that show the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Web Site and its individual pages. These aggregated statistics are used internally to improve our Web Site and for product development and marketing purposes generally. Those aggregated statistics may also be provided to advertisers and other third parties,but again,the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.  
   
b) Personal Information Collected   
In a few areas on our Web Site,we ask you to provide information that will enable us to verify whether you are entitled to access and use certain information,materials and services available from our Web Site,to enable us to enhance your site visit,to assist you with customer service or technical support issues,to follow up with you after your visit,or to otherwise support your customer relationship with us. Providing such information is completely optional. However,failure to provide it may mean that you cannot access and use certain information,materials and services.  
For example,we request information from you when you:

* Log-on to certain areas of our Web Site,such as the kenyalawreports.or.ke Research System,where you may be prompted to provide us with your Kenya Law Reports ID number and password as a condition to gaining access to certain information,materials or services

* Subscribe to a product information newsletter,ask to be added to our mailing lists to receive information about our products or services,register for a seminar or notify us of a change of address

* Place an order  
* Participate in a promotional offer  
* Provide feedback in an online survey

In each of the instances above,we typically ask for your name,e-mail address,phone number,address,law practice information,product preference information,as well as other similar personal information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. On occasion,we may ask for additional information to enable us to provide you with access to and use of certain information,materials and services. In the case of product information newsletters or direct or electronic mailing lists,you will be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings at any time.  
   
6.  **How We Use Personal Information**  
The National Council for Law Reporting uses your personal information only for specific purposes. The personal information you provide to us when using our Web Site,such as your name,postal or e-mail address or telephone number will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with Kenya Law Reports,and to notify you of special offers,updated information and new products and services from Kenya Law Reports,or offers from third parties that we think may be of interest to you. Agents or contractors of Kenya Law Reports who are given access to your personal information will be required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for Kenya Law Reports.  
Kenya Law Reports may enhance or merge your personal information collected at its Web Site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.

Circumstances may arise where we are required to disclose your personal information to third parties for purposes other than to support your customer relationship with us, such as in connection with a corporate divestiture or dissolution where we sell all or a portion of our business or assets (including our associated customer lists containing your personal information),or if disclosure is permitted or required by law (for example, in connection with judicial proceedings or governmental investigations).  
   
7. **  Opting Out or Unsubscribing**  
We will send you information about our various products and services or other products or services we feel may be of interest to you. Only the National Council for Law Reporting (or agents or contractors working on our behalf under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct or electronic mailings. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, you can request to be removed from either our direct or electronic mailing lists at any time by emailing us at marketing@kenyalaw.org

8.  **Our Commitment to Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy,and ensure the correct use of information,we have put into place appropriate procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online through firewalls and encryption technology.

9.  **Amendments**  
We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. Changes will be posted on this Web Site.

10 .  **How to Contact Us**  
If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices,to request a copy of the personal information that Kenya Law Reports has collected about you,or to have inaccuracies or omissions in this information corrected via the Internet,contact marketing@kenyalaw.org
